virginradiolebanon.com 2015-11-28

# Privacy Policy - Virgin Radio Lebanon

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Please take the time to read this privacy policy, which is part of our terms of use. By using the virginradiolb.com site, you are agreeing to be bound by the Terms and Conditions including this privacy policy. This policy explains how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us. ‘Personal information’ is information which identifies you or another person, or is capable of doing so.

This policy may change from time to time and, if it does, the up-to-date version will always be available on the virginradiolb.com site. Please note that by continuing to use virginradiolb.com site you are agreeing to any updated versions.

**What are cookies?**

We use “cookies” to store and collect information regarding your use of our site. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by the browser on your computer’s hard drive. They send the information stored on them back to our web server when you access our site. These cookies enable us to load the site in such a way as to reflect your personal preferences (based on your previous browsing on Virgin.com as well as keywords we may be able to gather from the URLs of webpages from which you accessed Virgin.com, your IP address and any search engine used to reach Virgin.com). We use these cookies to improve your experience on our site and recommend content that may be of interest to you. You can find out more about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org and more about the cookies we use below.

**What cookies do we use?**

We only set a few cookies ourselves, but when we include content from other sites (like Facebook or Twitter), they also get the opportunity to set cookies, to help them serve their content better. We’ve broken down the main uses of cookies you’ll see on the site below, and what they are used for, but we can’t guarantee that we’ll have listed every cookie you might get from a third party – they can change them at any time as their needs change.

**Cookies for Measuring Web Traffic**

We make use of a tool from Google called Google analytics which tells us about the way people are using virginradiolb.com

It uses cookies to detect that someone has been to the site before, so that we can see how often people return to the site, how long they stay, and where on virginradiolb.com they tend to go. We use this to try to work out what kind of experience they’re having on the site, so we can make it better.

Google Analytics sets cookies to help us accurately estimate the number of people visiting virginradiolb.com and let us see how they’re moving around the site. We use this when we make decisions on the type of content we create and how we structure the site.

**Cookies From Social Networks**

**Facebook**

We use Facebook social plugins on virginradiolb.com including the Like button, Facebook comments, recommendations and connect. Facebook will access some cookies if you have been to Facebook previously. If you haven’t visited Facebook, no cookies will be added. For more information about how Facebook uses cookies, please see their support site http://www.facebook.com/help/445588775451827.

**Twitter**

We make use of Twitter social plugins in order to be able to tweet through virginradiolb.com Twitter makes use of cookies to improve its own service. You can read more about how Twitter users cookies in their privacy policy  https://twitter.com/privacy

**Google+**

We include a Google+ plugin on many of our news and blog post pages to allow viewers to share links via that service. That plugin sets the following cookies, though you will get a different mix of cookies depending on whether you are logged in to Google and Google+, or not. For more information about the Google +1 button, see their privacy policy http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/+/policy/+1button.html

**Cookies For Adverts**

We have a number of spots around the site that show advertisements. These are managed through a system called Google Adsense. We use this banner advertisements.

**Cookies for Content**

We include content from other sites in our updates, most notably YouTube videos. When we do this, YouTube may store cookies in order to track how people are watching videos from their site.

**Will we share your information with anyone else?**

Only if…

You specifically request this, such as when you submit information to enquire about jobs or submit a job application through info@virginradiolb.com

We are required to do so to comply with the law or with the directions of the courts or other authorities

We feel it is reasonably necessary to prevent illegal activity or to protect our interests

Other Virgin companies products and services may interest you

It helps our trusted third party service providers to provide and improve our service to you or to carry out surveys and user analysis to understand your needs and preferences.

We may share some broader statistics and customer profiling information with third parties and other Virgin companies – but we’ll keep it anonymous, so you won’t be identifiable from that data.

We won’t rent or sell our user’s details to any other organization or individual.

What if you post information on our site?

This site contains an opportunity for users to comment on content on the site (“User Content”). It is information in the public domain, so it may be accessed by any person using the web in any part of the world and can be found using independent search engines. So, if you choose to post information to the interactive parts of our site, we have to state that you do so at your own risk. This is the case whether the User Content is uploaded directly onto virginradiolb.com or through a connected site.

However, if you upload User Content to our site using the Facebook Connect function, we will protect your privacy consistently with your Facebook privacy settings.

Please read our Terms and Conditions for more information about posting User Content.

If you have any concerns about User Content appearing on this site, please contact us on info@virginradiolb.com

**What about personal information relating to minors?**

Protecting the online privacy of children is especially important. If you are under 18 years old, please do not provide us with your name, contact details or any other information about yourself. To find out more, please read our Terms and Conditions.

**Are you protected by this policy outside virginradiolb.com?**

Our site contains links to other websites. Obviously, we don’t have any control over them and take no responsibility for any information you give them. Other sites have different privacy and security policies, which we advise you to read.

How you can access your information

You can request, at any time, access to the personal information we hold about you. You can write to us at the following address requesting access to your personal information.

If you have any queries, comments or complaints regarding this privacy policy, just get in touch. You can contact us on info@virginradiolb.com

This policy was last updated on 31 March 2015.
